[
    {
        "front": "lake",
        "back": "See"
    },
    {
        "front": "cloudy",
        "back": "bedeckt, bewölkt"
    },
    {
        "front": "around",
        "back": "um ... herum, umher"
    },
    {
        "front": "fire",
        "back": "Feuer"
    },
    {
        "front": "stick",
        "back": "Stock, Schläger"
    },
    {
        "front": "rock climbing",
        "back": "Klettern"
    },
    {
        "front": "arts and crafts",
        "back": "Kunsthantwerk"
    },
    {
        "front": "instead",
        "back": "stattdessen"
    },
    {
        "front": "photography contest",
        "back": "Fotowettbewerb"
    },
    {
        "front": "guy",
        "back": "Typ, Kerl, Leute"
    },
    {
        "front": "pyramid",
        "back": "Pyramide"
    },
    {
        "front": "mummy",
        "back": "Mumie"
    },
    {
        "front": "(to) joke",
        "back": "scherzen, Spaß machen"
    },
    {
        "front": "ride",
        "back": "Fahrt, Ritt"
    },
    {
        "front": "soon",
        "back": "bald"
    },
    {
        "front": "(to) teach",
        "back": "unterrichten, lehren, beibringen"
    },
    {
        "front": "trick",
        "back": "Kunststückchen"
    },
    {
        "front": "Guess what?",
        "back": "Weißt du was?"
    },
    {
        "front": "(to) guess",
        "back": "raten, erraten, vermuten"
    },
    {
        "front": "(to) give a high five",
        "back": "abklatschen, einschlagen"
    },
    {
        "front": "early",
        "back": "früh"
    },
    {
        "front": "(to) practise",
        "back": "üben, trainieren"
    },
    {
        "front": "coach",
        "back": "Trainer/-in"
    },
    {
        "front": "local",
        "back": "örtlich, lokal"
    },
    {
        "front": "news",
        "back": "Nachricht(en), Neuigkeit(en)"
    },
    {
        "front": "message",
        "back": "Botschaft, Nachricht"
    },
    {
        "front": "postcard",
        "back": "Postkarte"
    },
    {
        "front": "fun park",
        "back": "Freizeitpark"
    },
    {
        "front": "campsite",
        "back": "Zeltplatz, Campingplatz"
    },
    {
        "front": "mountian",
        "back": "Berg"
    },
    {
        "front": "forest",
        "back": "Wald"
    },
    {
        "front": "tent",
        "back": "Zelt"
    },
    {
        "front": "north",
        "back": "Norden, Nord-"
    },
    {
        "front": "south",
        "back": "Süden, Süd-"
    }
]
